database = [
    {
        question: 'What is the series of events in a story known as?',
        optionA: 'Setting',
        optionB: 'Plot',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the topic or lesson in a story?',
        optionA: 'Theme',
        optionB: 'Plot',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'What are words which create mental images known as?',
        optionA: 'Background',
        optionB: 'Imagery',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'What are the people in a story called who are not apart of the main story?',
        optionA: 'Minor Character',
        optionB: 'Backup',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the character which the story revolves around?',
        optionA: 'Minor Character',
        optionB: 'Major Character',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct definition for the word: “Abandon”',
        optionA: 'To leave someone or something',
        optionB: 'To stop fighting',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct definition for the word: “Accumulate”',
        optionA: 'To stop doing nice things',
        optionB: 'To collect or gather',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct definition for the word: “Academy”',
        optionA: 'A place to play',
        optionB: 'A school',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct definition for the word: “Adapt”',
        optionA: 'A place to train',
        optionB: 'To change or adjust',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct definition for the word: “Activate”',
        optionA: 'To start something',
        optionB: 'To stop something',
        answer: 'A'
    }
]